webhostface.com 2019-08-15

# WebHostFace Privacy Policy

WebHostFace Privacy Policy

### 1\. Gathering information

This Privacy Policy is intended to inform you of our policies and practices regarding the collection and use of any personal information we obtain about you based upon your use of WebHostFace.com LLC website, services or products. All policies in regards to collecting and storing personal information are in compliance with The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (EU) and the FTC Act. You are referred to below as “Subscriber”.

### 1.1 How do we define personal data?

Personal data is any information that relates to an identified or identifiable living individual. Different pieces of information, which collected together can lead to the identification of a particular person, also constitute personal data.

### 1.2 What is the personal data collected and stored by WebHostFace?

WebHostFace only collects data which is necessary for providing the Subscriber with the services they order, and one that is used to secure ownership of all product purchased at the WebHostFace website, including hosting accounts, domain names, additional services or any other service or product provided by WebHostFace. This includes Subscriber’s name, company name, physical address, e-mail address and telephone number, billing information provided by the Subscriber upon signing up for the service or changed by the Subscriber at a later stage. Copies of identity documents, citizen cards, international passports, drivers licenses or other formal documents may be requested and kept for additional validation of the Subscriber. For the purposes of on-time payments for services and product on the WebHostFace website, WebHostFace also may store payment information. Payment information can be removed at all times upon request made by the Subscriber. Additionally, WebHostFace may storе transaction information for purchases the Subscriber makes on the WebHostFace website or offline, emails sent to WebHostFace, chat transcripts, telephone call recordings, as well as other information that is non–public, such as IP addresses, URL, browser information, activity on the WebHostFace website, etc. All this information is collected with the consent of the Subscriber through order forms, emails, chats, telephone conversations, payments, etc.   
WebHostFace does not systematically collect information about the Subscriber’s religious beliefs, political views, posts on social networking websites, medical information, sexual orientations, etc. Some personal information might be collected through cookies, which are small pieces of data that are sent to your browser from a web server and are stored on your computer’s hard drive. By visiting the WebHostFace website, the Subscriber consents to the usage of cookies. Cookies may be deleted at all times from the Subscriber’s browser.

### 1.3 HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

All personal data collected by WebHostFace is used solely for the purpose of providing the services purchased by the Subscriber in a timely and uninterrupted manner, to provide support to secure the ownership of the Subscriber’s account and data and to facilitate a convenient, user-friendly, and practical customer experience. All personal information, such as Subscriber’s name, company name, physical address, e-mail address and telephone number are used to secure ownership of the Subscriber over the hosting account, domain name/s and other services purchased on the WebHostFace website, as well as all passwords, usernames, data, and configuration of the hosting account. Subscriber’s names, emails, and telephone number may be used to send transactional notices about your account, reminders of expiring services, account information, email newsletters, and news of special promotions offered through WebHostFace and/or in conjunction with WebHostFace’s partners. The subscriber can unsubscribe from WebHostFace newsletters and promotional mailings by contacting WebHostFace or through the unsubscribe links provided in promotional email messages sent by WebHostFace or on WebHostFace’s behalf. 

Reviews of WebHostFace services written by the Subscriber may be used for marketing purposes. Billing information is used to provide uninterrupted service, avoid transaction issues and missed deadlines. All billing information (such as credit/debit card information and PayPal subscription) can be removed upon request of the Subscriber. By using credit/debit card, PayPal, or another payment method, the Subscriber gives consent to WebHostFace to store this information and use it to renew hosting accounts, domain names and other services purchased by the Subscriber. Copies of identity documents, citizen cards, international passports, drivers licenses or other formal documents may be requested by WebHostFace representatives and used solely for the verification of the Subscriber’s payment information, ownership information or legal age. No such copies will be disclosed to third parties, unless they are required by law or as proof of the legitimacy of an online payment made by the Subscriber. 

Communication between the Subscriber and WebHostFace via email, chat, telephone or tickets is used to provide information, solve Subscriber concerns or problems, and answer Subscriber’s questions. Such communication may also be used to improve the service and user experience, for staff training and marketing purposes. By uploading content and software on the hosting account, the Subscriber is consenting to WebHostFace gathering and storing this data. Storage of data is used only for in order to provide the service and access to it is not provided to third parties unless explicitly consented by the Subscriber. In the event of voluntary or involuntary illegal activities by the Subscriber, the stored data may be deleted from WebHostFace servers. 

By registering a domain name you agree to comply with global domain regulations, which mandate personal information be available in WHOIS databases. Subscriber’s visits and activity on the WebHostFace website may be used to develop marketing strategies and tailor services or information to Subscriber’s location. WebHostFace may also share Subscriber’s personal information with trusted vendors or partners in order for them to provide you with services, offers that we think you will find valuable or in order to optimize WebHostFace services.The use of any data provided by WebHostFace to these partnering companies and vendors is governed by their own Privacy Policies and is beyond WebHostFace’s control.

### 1.4 HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR PERSONAL DATA?

WebHostFace takes your privacy seriously. When the Subscriber orders from WebHostFace.com LLC, Personal Data Transmissions are encrypted. WebHostFace.com LLC uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), the industry standard, for encrypting all customer information, including personal name, address, telephone number, company name and billing information. Our database is encrypted monitored and protected from data breaches. All sensitive information is protected by encryption and passwords. No personal or account information is changed or disclosed without the explicit consent of the Subscriber and only after their careful verification. 

Ownership of the above services is solely provided to the person recorded in our system to be the account owner and no third parties. All WebHostFace members are trained and instructed to act in accordance with the above privacy policies. Personal and account information is only accessible by WebHostFace staff and 24/7 under monitoring conditions. There might be, however, security and privacy limitations, which are beyond the scope of WebHostFace. 

WebHostFace will provide personal information if mandated by law. By providing your personal information the Subscriber is aware and understands that WebHostface cannot 100% guarantee absolute security, integrity, and privacy of the information in cases which are beyond our control.

### 1.5 Secure Partners Data Sharing Only

In order to offer and provide services that are listed on our site, some of your data can be shared with external providers likes domain registrars, SSL providers, content delivery network (CDN) providers. All our partners have implemented GDPR-compliant standards way before the actual law was introduced, or have signed a special contract with us to meet our data protection standards.

### 1.6 Processing of uploaded data on your account

As a hosting provider we have responsibility as a data processor. As a GDPR requirement, we have specific criteria to meet due to the websites hosted on our servers that store any personal data on WebHostFace servers. The obligations are described in our Data Processing Agreement.

## Data Processing Agreement

### 1\. Data Processing Agreement

Up to date and Transparent Security Measures As a reliable web hosting provider and data processing company we have implemented the highest possible up-to-date security standards in order to provide adequate security measures for the data uploaded on our servers by our customers. WebHostFace shall implement and maintain technical and organizational measures to protect Customer Data against accidental or unlawful destruction, loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access. The Security Measures include measures to provide encrypted transmission of customer data outside the Service environment; to help ensure ongoing confidentiality, integrity, availability and resilience of WebHostFace’s systems and services; to help restore timely access to Customer Data from an available backup copy, provided either by WebHostFace Backup Services or Customer’s own backup copy following an incident; and for regular testing of effectiveness. WebHostFace may update or modify the Security Measures from time to time provided that such updates and modifications do not result in the degradation of the overall security of the Services.Minimum Access Principle The DPA puts in writing our obligation to access any data that our customers store on our servers only to the extent needed to provide our services and to make sure only employees that are directly involved with the provision of the service have access to it. WebHostFace shall not access or use Customer Data, except as necessary to provide the Services and related technical support to the Customer in accordance with the DPA, the Agreement and other relevant policies.We Provide Access To Secure Partners Only Our partnering companies might need access to the data uploaded on our servers so that we can provide our service. Our data center partners are an example of such a partnering company. We provide access only to partners that have same or higher level of data protection as the one we guarantee you through our DPA. WebHostFace Partners may be retained as Sub-processors; and WebHostFace and WebHostFace Partners respectively may engage Sub-processors in connection with the provisioning of the Services. WebHostFace has entered into a written agreement with each Sub-processor containing data protection obligations not less protective than those in this DPA with respect to the protection of Customer Data to the extent applicable to the nature of the Services provided by such Sub-processors.Any Personal Data Breach Is Timely Disclosed Our DPA responsibilities include timely disclosure by WebHostFace, if a personal data breach is detected by us to have happened on the servers used by our clients. We are obliged to notify our affected customers within 72 hours.Any End User GDPR Requests Are Appropriately Passed On Also if WebHostFace receives a request by an individual, using a website hosted on our servers, to exercise one of the personal data rights outlined in the GDPR, we’ll redirect them to the site owner.Our DPA Helps You Become GDPR-Compliant Our new DPA does not make sites hosted by us GDPR compliant on its own. Our customers, as site owners, are solely responsible to apply the GDPR principles in processing their European users’ personal information. However, even if you have done your part on making your website GDPR compliant, it will not be fully there, unless your hosting provider has a DPA.

Read Data Processing Agreement

### 4\. Cookie Policy and Tracking

4.1 WebHostFace uses different types of cookies (which are electronic collections of information stored on a local computer that are used by websites to keep track of visitors and registered users and to relate one computer transaction to a later one) and other methods of uniquely tracking visitors for different purposes. For example, some cookies are “required cookies” which are necessary for WebHostFace’s website to work. In addition, cookies are used to provide WebHostFace’s existing Subscribers with the opportunity for continued savings and increased convenience as described in more detail below.

### 4.2 Cookies for Improving Our Web Site

WebHostFace uses “performance cookies” to inform WebHostFace of a repeat visit. However, these cookies do not tell WebHostFace who a visitor is, the visitor’s name, email address, or passwords.

### 4.3 Cookies for Banner Rewards Program

To offer WebHostFace Subscribers continued savings, WebHostFace uses cookies to help monitor the traffic generated from WebHostFace banners and logo buttons displayed on WebHostFace Subscribers’ websites.

### 4.4 Cookies for Subscriber Account Management

For WebHostFace Subscribers, WebHostFace uses “functional cookies” to store user names for added convenience. For example, the cookie would contain a piece of identifying information such as a customer ID, username, or session ID that would be used to look up the customer ID. WebHostFace offers password-protected, web-based management tools as part of its webhosting packages. By storing a Subscriber’s username in a cookie, the Subscriber will not have to fill out form fields each time he or she manages the account. (The cookie does not store passwords.)

### 4.5 Cookies for Advertising

WebHostFace may also utilize “advertising cookies” to track referrals from internal and external affiliates, as well as advertising campaigns. We may also use a third party service provider to send emails that you have agreed to receive. Pixel tags and cookies may be used in those email messages to help us measure the effectiveness of its advertising and to enable WebHostFace to provide more focused marketing communications to you.

### 5\. Third Parties

Information collected on this site is strictly for our use, NO OTHER OUTSIDE PERSONS MAY VIEW YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION SUCH BILLING INFORMATION, ETC. Links To Other Sites: Our Site may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit. WebHostFace.com LLC has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party sites or services.

### 6\. Privacy Policy changes

WebHostFace LLC reserves the right to change that Privacy Policy and publish the changes on our website. It is Subscriber’s responsibility to review those on regular basis and agree with all the changes published.To report an incident of abuse, please email abuse@webhostface.com
